Guide to the Hoover Institution Archives Photograph Card Catalog
Hoover Institution Archives
- Gregory (Thomas T. C.) Collection, undated; 4 prints / 2 envelopes / 1 photo album (Box 72059 - 10 A-V)
  - 1 photo of T.T.C. Gregory and 1 photo of crowd scene in front of Hoover house at Stanford on election night, 1928 (Folder mB)
  - 1 album of photos of billboards prepared by the Foster and Kleiser Co. for the 1928 Hoover Presidential Campaign (Folder fC)
- Griffin, R. Allen Collection, 32 prints, 9 negatives / 3 envelopes (Box 75027 - 10.A-V)
  - 19 prints of R. Allen Griffin; 1 print of R. Allen Griffin with unidentified man; 2 negatives, undated (Folder A)
  - 1 group print of Mr. and Mrs. Roger D. Lapham, Mr. and Mrs. R. Allen Griffin and others during U.S. Economic Cooperation Administration - China Mission, 1948-1949; 3 prints of R. Allen Griffin and others signing contracts related to U.S. Economic Cooperation Administration - China, 1948-1949; 5 prints of Paul G. Hoffman's visit to China, December, 1948, including group prints with Chiang Kai-shek, Li Tsung-jen, J. Leighton Stuart and Roger D. Lapham; 1 group print of R. Allen Griffin, Henry T. Samson, Roger D. Lapham, Dr. Sun of, Lewis Clark, Wu Te-chen; 7 negatives (Folder mB)
  - 2 miscellaneous prints, undated (Folder C)
- Grose (ADA M.) Collection, 12 photos / 13 negatives / 1 envelope / 1 album (107 prints and 3 clippings in album) (Box XX145 - 8.05)
  - 13 photos and negatives depicting events of and persons involved in the Henry Ford Peace Expedition and the Neutral Conference for Continuous Mediation, circa 1915
    Includes photos of Ford, Thomas A. Edison, William Jennings Bryan. 3 of the negatives do not have corresponding photos. One negative of the route of the peace ship Oscar II. Prints are labeled
  - Album depicting voyage of ship and conference, undated (Folder f)
- Grossmann, Kurt Richard Collection, undated; 42 prints / 1 envelope (Box 75026 - 10.A-V)
  42 prints of Kurt R. Grossmann, Willy Brandt, Carl von Ossietzky and others.
- Guins, George C. Collection, undated; 37 photographs / 1 envelope (Box XX314 - 10.A-V)
  2 prints of Admiral Aleksandr K. Kolchak; 1 print of General Mikhail K. Dietrichs; 1 print of General Jan Syrovy; 1 print of P.V. Vologodskago; 1 print of Ivan I. Serebrennikov; 1 print of Lev M. Mikhailov; 1 print of Zefirov; 1 print of Steponenkol 1 print of Gudkov; 1 print of Gratsianov; 1 print of Shchmelovsky; 1 print of Sapoznikov; 1 print of Potushchapsky; 2 unidentified prints of people; 22 prints of scenes in Siberia.
- Gunther, Wilhelmina Collection, circa 1905; 2 prints / 1 envelope (Box 90008 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  2 prints of the Russian revolutionist Wilhelmina Gunther.
- Haislip (Wade H.) Collection, 25 prints / 1 envelope / 1 album (Box 74051 - 10.A-V)
  - 12 prints of General Wade H. Haislip in group and individual photos, including 1 print of nine former Seventh Army Commanders taken at Heidelberg, Germany, 1968; 1 group photo of General Haislip with Generals George S. Patton and Jacques-Phillipe Leclerc, circa 1945 (Folder A)
  - Photo album presented to General Haislip in Commemoration of the visit of the former Seventh Army Commanders to the Daimler-Benz Aktiengesellschaft in Stuttgart, Germany, November 11-13, 1968 (Folder fB)
- Hall, Charles L Collection, 1920s; 26 prints / 1 envelope (Box 64024 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of Major Charles L. Hall and other American Relief Administration workers in Orenburg and Samara, Russia, famine victims in these areas, and ARA supplies being loaded.
- Hammon (W. P.) Collection, 367 prints / 5 envelopes / 276 negatives / 2 envelopes (Box 72007 - 10 A-V)
  - 55 photos of mining and land reclamation projects in Siberia, 1921-22 (Folder A)
  - 70 photos of scenes in daily life in Siberia, circa 1920 (Box B)
  - 500 photos of dredging equipment sent to the U.S.S.R. from the United States, circa 1947 (Folder C-F)
  - 24 prints of American and European political leaders, 1921-1935 (Box G)
- Hammond (Lansing V.) Collection, 1900-1940; 2 file boxes / 4 file drawers / photos and drawings (Box 57012 - 8.09)
  Collection of photographs and drawings of British, Russian, Japanese, German, U.S. and other ships and airplanes from W.W. II, and a section of photos on the history of aviation. 4 file drawers.
- Hanna, Paul Robert Collection, undated; 697 prints / 21 envelopes / 3 albums (Box 77098 - 10.A-V)
- Hansen, Joseph Collection, undated; 58 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 92035 - 10.A-V)
  - 15 prints of Joseph Hansen family members, and childhood home, undated (Folder A)
    Includes 3 prints taken at Intercontinental Press banquet, showing Joseph and Reba Hansen and George Novack.
  - 14 prints, including 1 of George Breitman; 2 of Evelyn Redd and Ch'en Pi-lan; 1 of Peng Shu-tse and Ch'en Pi-lan; 1 of Earnest and Gisela Mandel; 1 of Gisela Mandel; 3 of Gerry Healy; 1 of Hugo Gonzalez Moscoso; 1 of Felipe (Bolivian Trotskyist); 1 of prisoners in Lecumberri prison, Mexico City, with "Trostky" banner, 1969; 1 of detail from Diego Rivera mural depicting Leon Trotsky and Fourth International banner; and 1 of satirical; drawings by Edwin Herron (Box B)
  - 29 miscellaneous prints, undated (Folder C)
- Harris (David) Collection, undated; 6 envelopes (Box 67000 - 10.)
  - 1 print of Benito Mussolini, undated (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Adolf Hitler as Reich Chancellor, undated (Box B)
  - 1 print of Paul von Hindenburg as Reich President, undated (Folder C)
  - 1 print of Kaiser Franz Josef and 2 prints of Kaiserin Elisabeth, undated (Box D)
  - Prints depicting David Harris, undated (Folder E-mF)
- Harris, Ernest Lloyd Collection, undated; 16 prints, 4 negatives / 1 envelope (Box XX072 - 10.A-V)
  16 prints, including 6 photographs of Consul General Harris' first wife, 4 group photographs including Consul General Harris, one with Admiral Kolchak and one with U.S. consular officials, 1 photograph of the entrance to the Mosque of Selim at Ephesus, and a photograph of Consul General Harris with his second wife.
- Harris, Gladys Collection, 1919; 20 prints / 1 envelope (Box m78071 - 10.A-V)
  20 prints taken by the U.S. Army Signal Corps of the headquarters of the American Expeditionary Forces, Siberia, and of officers of the Japanese and Czechoslovak forces, Vladivostok.
- Harrison, Alexander Collection, 128 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 84063 - 10.A-V)
  - 49 color photographs of former leaders of the Organization Armee Secrete and of sites in Algeria associated with O.A.S. activities, 1978-1984 (Folder A)
  - 59 color photographs of former leaders of the O.A.S, undated (Box B)
  - 20 prints depicting former leaders of the O.A.S, undated (Folder C)
- Hart, Jeffrey Collection, undated; 3 print / 1 envelope (Box 81103 - Photo file Envelope A)
  3 prints depicting Jeffrey Hart, including one with John Sununu.
- Hasenkamp, Bruce H. Collection, 1963-1965; 1 manuscript box (Box 99034 - 16.224 Box 1)
  Prints of armistice negotiation meetings and other scenes in the demilitarized zone between North and South Korea.
- Hayek, Friedrich A. von Collection, 9 prints / 5 envelopes (Box 86002 - Photo file)
  For additional photos, see register for increment to this collection.
  - 2 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek, undated (Folder A)
  - 4 prints depicting Friedrich A. von Hayek addressing a group in Argentina, 1977 (Box B)
  - 1 print depicting the room in the Institute for Wirtschaftswissenshcaften at the University of Salzburg, Austria, in which Friedrich A. von Hayek's personal library is housed, 1980 (Folder C)
  - 1 print depicting Ludwig von Bertalanffy with his staff, undated (Box D)
  - 1 print depicting Margit and Ludwig von Mises, 1972 (Box E)
- Hayes (Elinor) Collection, 1 envelope / 2 prints (Box 72011 - 9.23)
  2 photos including one of a shell hole made by a Japanese submarine shell at the Ellwood Oil Fields, Santa Barbara, California, February 1942, and another of General Jack W. Heard at Camp Cook.
- Healy (James A.) Collection, 1938; 3 prints / 1 envelope (Box XX234 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  3 photos of Herbert Hoover, either alone or with Mrs. (Lou Henry) Hoover, or with his family at Christmas.
- Hegland, Sheridan Collection, June 17, 1988; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 87003 - 10.A-V)
  1 print depicting Sheridan Hegland and his wife Edwinda K. Hegland upon receiving honorary degrees from Southwestern Community College.
- Heinz, Luther Carl Collection, undated; 1 album (Box 80143 - 8M.02)
  Depicts U.S. Navy ships and personnel.
- Herbits, Stephen E. Collection, undated; 1 print / 1 envelope (Box 75065 - Photo file Envelope A)
  1 print depicting Byron V. Pepitone, acting director, National Selective Service.
- Herr (Horace H.) Collection, 1924-25; 192 prints / 3 envelopes (Box 76006 - 10.A-V Envelope A-C)
  192 photographs depicting H. H. Herr's travels in Northern Africa.
- Higgins (Frank H.) Collection, 13 photos / 2 envelopes (Box 69007 - 10 A-V)
  - 8 photos of Col. Frank H. Higgins in Japan, Alabama, etc. and at a reception in his honor, undated (Folder A)
    Includes photo of Sec. of the army W. M. Brucker.
  - 4 photos of W. M. Brucker, Gen. Maxwell Taylor, and Gen. William Westmoreland, undated (Folder B, m)
  - 1 photo of the U.S. Army Policy Council, March 21, 1956 (Folder m* dr. 3)
- Hill, Margaret E. Collection, undated; 162 prints, 15 negatives / 9 envelopes (Box 79071 - 10.A-V)
  - 15 negatives depicting World War II relief activities, undated (Folder A)
  - 26 prints of a United Nations War Relief Council fund-raising exhibition, undated (Box B)
  - 15 prints of relief activities in Calais, France, after World War II, undated (Folder C)
  - 32 prints of officials and activities of the United Nations War Relief Council, undated (Box D)
  - 28 prints of World War II relief activities in France, undated (Box E)
  - 22 prints of World War II relief activities in Norway, undated (Box 79071 - 10.A-V, Box F)
  - 20 prints of World War II relief activities in Czechoslovakia, undated (Box G)
  - 9 prints of World War II relief activities in Poland, undated (Box H)
  - 21 prints of World War II relief activities in various countries, undated (Box I)
- Hill, Robert Charles Collection, circa 2000 prints / 5 albums, 73 envelopes (Box 79067 - 10.A-V)
- Hillhouse, (Joseph Newton) Collection, undated; 507 prints / 1 album (Box 64019 - 10.A-V Album f)
  1 photo album of World War I photographs depicting the activities of the A.E.F. in France, includes scenes of war destruction, and significant individuals such as, Woodrow Wilson, John J. Pershing, Ferdinand Foch, and Georges Clemenceau.
- Himmler (Heinrich) Collection, 1929-1936, undated; 237 photos / 2 albums (Box XX060 - Vault)
  237 prints depicting the career of Heinrich Himmler as Reichsfuhrer-SS and Chef der Deutschen Polizei. Original photo albums closed; digital use copies available.
- Hindenburg, Paul Von Collection, undated (Box XX009 - Map case m*A)
  1 print of Paul von Hindenburg
- Hitler, Adolf, 223 prints / 14 negatives / 5 envelopes (Box XX237 - 10.A-V)
  - 41 prints depicting Adolf Hitler, his family, his teachers and various villages, 1889-1938 (Folder A)
    Includes 10 prints of Hitler in his youth, 5 prints of Hitler's father, 2 prints of Hitler's mother, 1 print of the Hitler house.
  - 9 prints depicting Adolf Hitler with German Troops, undated (Box B)
  - 170 prints depicting Adolf Hitler as Fuehrer and Chancellor of Germany, undated (Folder C)
    Includes 2 prints of Joseph Goebbels and his family.
  - 1 print of Adolf Hitler at the Reichsparteitag, 1934 (Box D)
  - 3 prints of Adolf Hitler. 1 print of Hitler in Germany, 1940; 1 print of Hitler with Benito (Box E)
- Hodges (Charles) Collection, 1,076 prints / 53 envelopes (Box 64001 - 10.A-V)
  1,076 prints of World War II, 1939-1945, depicting scenes in Europe, North Africa, Far East, Southeast Asia, Pacific Islands, India, and the Aleutian Islands; covering events such as the Potsdam Conference 1945 and the Casablanca Conference 1943 and portraying various civilian and military leaders, scenes of destruction, scenes of surrender, Alcan highway. Includes a World War II map series. Inventory available.
- Holden, F. H. Collection, 1916-1917; 28 prints / 1 envelope (Box 56031 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of the German cruiser Wolf, its crew, and ships encountered and sunk by the Wolf during its raiding cruise in World War I.
- Holman, Benjamin Collection, undated; 7 prints / 1 envelope (Box 85032 Envelope A)
  7 photos of Benjamin Holman.
- Holman, Emile Collection, circa 100 prints / 1 envelope (Box 63022 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of refugees and war damage in Greece, Bulgaria and Turkey at the end of the Balkan Wars of 1912-1913 and of the visit of David Starr Jordan, Emile Holman and others to the war site, 1914.
- Holtzmann, Robert Collection, undated; 15 photographs / 2 envelopes (Box 49015 - 10.A-V)
  - 11 photos including 2 photos of Adolf Hitler; 4 photos of Erich Ludendorff; 5 photos of members of the Tannenbergbund, undated (Folder A)
  - Print of Erich Ludendorff; a photo of Adolf Hitler and World War I German officers, undated (Folder mB)
- Home front, W.W. I Collection, 1917-1918; 5 prints / 1 envelope (Box XX074 - 10.)
  5 prints depicting scenes on the U.S. homefront in Cincinnati. Prints are labeled.
- Honens (W. H.) Collection, November 1916-1917; 1,109 prints / 3 albums (Box 76113 - 8M.02 Albums fA-C)
  1,109 photographs depicting the activities of the Stanford Ambulance Service Unit, U.S. Army, and other scenes, during WWI in France and Albania.
- Honey, John K Collection, undated; 692 prints, 143 negatives / 3 envelopes (Box 79063 - 10.A-V Envelope A-C)
  Photographs of American and French troops, the ambulance service of the American Field Service, and scenes of destruction in France during World War I.
- Hoo, Victor Collection, 1940s-1960s; 36 prints / 1 envelope (Box 77046 - Photo file Envelope A)
  36 prints depicting Victor Hoo, alone and with others, especially at United Nations functions and meetings.
- Hook Sidney Collection, undated; 19 prints, 6 contact sheets, 15 postcards / 2 envelopes (Box 90003 - 10.A-V)
  - 6 contact sheets, and 17 prints of Sidney Hook and others, circa 1930s-1987; 1 print of Herbert Solow, John MacDonald, Jean van Heijenoort and others in Mexico, 1938; 15 postcards (7 duplicates) of scenes of Korea and Lebanon, undated (Folder A)
  - 1 print of Sidney Hook by Alfred Eisenstaedt, 1956 (Folder mB)
- Hoover (Herbert C.) Subject Collection, 3,363 photos / 162 negatives /2 film strips (92 envelopes, 1 album) (Box 62008 - 10.A-V)
  See register for listing of photographs.
- Hoover, Herbert Clark Collection, undated; 1 photo / no envelope (Box 70040 - 10.A-V dr. 2)
  1 photo dedicated to Mrs. Edward Bango Drew and signed by Herbert Hoover.
- Hoover, Lou Henry Collection, 31 prints / 1 envelope (Box XX656 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  1 print depicting Lou Henry Hoover in London circa 1900 and 30 prints depicting the Lou Henry Hoover House on Stanford Campus.
- Hornbeck (Stanley K.) Collection, 889 photos / 25 envelopes / 8 oversize photos (Box 67008 - 10.A-V)
- Hoskin (Harry L.) Collection, 809 prints / 7 envelopes (Box 76076 - 10.A-V)
  - 378 photos depicting scenes in Siberia, collected by H. Hoskin during his association with the Russian Railway Service Corps, 1917-1920 (Folder A-C)
  - 431 photos depicting scenes in Japan, the Philippine Islands, Hawaii and Guam, undated (Folder D-G)
- Houston, John Pollard Collection, undated; 20 prints / 1 oversize box, 1 oversize folder; 1 framed print (Box 95035 - 102.05, art racks, map case)
  - 18 prints, primarily depicting American military aircraft, and scenes of aircraft construction and of aeronautical research, undated (Folder 1)
  - 1 photo montage depicting Admiral William S. Sims and ships at rest in Navy yard, Philadelphia, 1919-1920. 1 print depicting the view of the Franconia mountain range from the Forest Hills Hotel in New Hampshire, undated (Folder Map case)
  - 1 framed print depicting the Atlantic Coast Aeronautical Station, 1917 (Folder Art rack 20, front)
- Howe, Esther B. Collection, undated; 1 prints /1 envelope (Box 70042 - 10.A-V Envelope mA)
  1 portrait of Lou Henry Hoover, dedicated to Mrs. Edward Bango Drew.
- Huenergardt, Mrs. John F. Collection, undated; 3 prints / 1 envelope (Box 57018 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of relief activities and infant famine victims in Hungary at the end of World War I.
- Hughes (James C.) Collection, undated; 1 envelope / 3 prints, 1 negative (Box 73017 - 10 v.)
  4 photos of Col. James C. Hughes during World War II.
- Huldermann (Paul) Collection, 166 prints / 2 envelopes (Box 38002 - 10.A-V)
  - 60 prints depicting conditions in the Republic of China. Register, 1936 (Folder A)
  - 106 prints depicting conditions in the Republic of China in 1936 and during the Sino-Japanese Conflict, 1937-45. Most prints are labeled (Box B)
- Hunt, Edward Eyre Collection, undated; 3 prints / 1 envelope (Box 56008 - 10.A-V)
  1 photo of The President's Research Committee on Social Trends; 1 print of J. Healy; 1 miscellaneous print.
- Huston (Jay Calvin) Collection, 16 prints / 2 envelopes (Box 47005 - 10 A-V)
  - 1 print of J. C. Huston, undated (Folder A)
  - 15 prints accompanying dispatch no. 699, December 30, 1927, describing the revolt of peasants, workers, and soldiers on December 11-13, 1927 at Canton (Folder mB)
- Hutchinson, J. Kent Collection, undated; 1 manuscript box and 1 projector in box. (Box XX286 - 8.21)
  Glass slides depicting scenes of daily life and agricultural and other economic activities in Japan and a variety of other Asian countries.
- Hutchinson (John Raymond) Collection, 22 prints / 2 envelopes (Box 52002 - 9.13)
  - 2 photos depicting the Arch of Victory at 5th Ave. and 23rd Street in New York City, 1899 and 1919 (Folder A)
  - 20 photos depicting transmitting apparatus for radio, telephone, and television; also, some scenes of apparatus in operation, 1927-1946 (Box B)
- Imperial War Museum, Great Britian photographs, 1915-1919; 1,552 prints / 32 envelopes (Box 62009 - 10.A-V)
  See register for list of photographs
- Indian National Congress. Foreign Relations Department. Collection, 1950-52; 166 photos / 1 envelope (Box XX147 - 10.AV)
  166 photos depicting events and persons involved in the Indian National Congress.
- Inglis (John and Theodora) Collection, 1900; 31 photos / 1 envelope (Box 73085 - 10 A-V)
  31 photos of scenes in China at the time of the Boxer Rebellion.
- Inglis, Thomas B. Collection, 4 prints / 1 envelope (Box 85059 - 10.A-V Envelope A)
  1 print depicting Thomas B. Inglis upon his promotion to Rear Admiral, 2 November 1945; and 3 prints depicting the ceremony held in the Soviet Embassy in Washington, D.C., December 7, 1945, during which the Soviet attache Nikolai V. Novikov presented Rear Admiral Inglis with 190 medals awarded to U.S. naval officers for "outstanding military activities in transporting goods to Murmansk"
- International Exhibition of Water Technics, Liege Collection, 1939; 1 album (Box XX410 - 8.24)
  Album of drawings and reproductions of photographs prepared for the International Exhibition of Water Technics held at Liege, Belgium, depicting scenes in Liege and illustrating the history of the city.
- International Military Tribunal. Far East. (Tokyo Trials) Collection, October 1945; 4 prints / 1 envelope (Box 47008 - 10.)
  4 prints depicting activities of the International Military Tribunal in Japan, including photos of war criminals.
- International Peace Conference Collection, 2 photographs, 1 canvas identification chart (Box SX181 - Art Racks)
  Two large glass framed photographs of the first and second Hague Peace Conferences 1899 and 1907, and an identification chart for the persons pictured in the framed photo of the Deuxieme conference de la Paix a la Haye 1907.
- Iran. Embassy Collection, undated; 4 photographs / 1 envelope (Box 79064 - 10.A-V)
  Depicts buildings and art objects in Iran.
- Iraq Collection, undated; 24 slides / 1 envelope (Box XX675 - 10.A-V)
  Depicts scenes in Iraq
- Irimescu (Radu) Collection, 837 prints / 5 albums / 1 envelopes (Box 75090 - 10.A-V)
- Italian Bureau of Information, New York City, Collection, 4 envelopes / 178 photographs (Box 60020 - 10.A-V)
  - 136 prints depicting activities of the Italian Army in World War I, including scenes of mountain warfare, 1915-1918 (Folder A)
  - 36 post cards depicting activities of the Italian Army in the Alps in World War I, 1915-1918 (Box B)
  - 4 prints of Woodrow Wilson, 1915 (Folder C)
  - 2 post cards of the children of the Italian royal family, 1915 (Box D)
- Jacobs (Fenton Stratton) Collection, 1933-1934 (Box 66022 - 10.Map cab. m*)
  1 oversize print depicting class members of the Command and General Staff School at Fort Leavenworth, Kansas.
- Japan. Consulate, San Francisco Collection, 1980; 4 prints / 1 envelope (Box 80099 - 10.A-V)
  Photographs of Prime Minister Masayoshi Ohira, Foreign Minister Saburo Okita, and Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary Koichi Kato of Japan.
- Jarvis (Charles E.) Collection, 39 photo-postcards / 2 envelopes (Box 60013 - 8.05)
  - 20 scenes of Verdun, France following bombardments, 1914-1918 (Folder A)
  - 19 scenes of the towns of Ham, Rosieres, Nesle and Fresnieres along the river Somme in France following the battles there. Prints labeled in French and English, 1916-1918 (Box B)
- Jennings (Ralph E.) Collection, undated; 200 prints / 4 albums / 400 prints /9 envelopes (Box 71059 - 9.23)
  - 4 albums: album entitled, "Souvenir of the Visit of the American Fleet to Tzinir, Sept 1947," 20 prints; album of scenes of Turkey, 24 prints; album concerning Jennings' mission to Turkey to reorganize the Turkish navy, 34 prints; and a commemorative album of the USS Yorktown wartime activities, 120 prints (Folder f)
  - 19 prints of Adm. Jennings and other important persons; 40 prints of crew members; 30 prints of USS Saratoga and USS Yorktown; 48 prints of ceremonies involving Adm. Jennings; 97 prints concerning visitations of Adm. Jennings' shops to foreign and domestic ports; 34 prints of World War II naval combat scenes; 70 aerial photos of bombing raids conducted by planes from the USS Yorktown; 12 prints of aircraft, undated (Folder A-H)
  - 1 envelope of 40 prints of World War II combat scenes; 1 picture book, "U.S. Navy War photographs, Pearl Harbor to Tokyo Harbor.", undated (Folder mI)
  - 5 prints (oversize and not in envelope) including a group photo of participants in the 1928 National Air Races, aerial photos of naval maneuvers, and 2 photos of maps (Folder dr. m1)
- Arnold E. Jenny Collection, 236 prints, 41 negatives / 3 envelopes (Box 73068 - 10.AV)
  85 prints depicting the activities of the Y.M.C.A contingent attached to the American Expeditionary Force in Siberia, 1919-1920; 90 prints depicting the activities of the Y.M.C.A and the U.N.R.R.A for displaced persons in Germany, 1945-46 and 20 miscellaneous prints.
- Jessey (Joseph) Collection, 1923 (Box 75019 - 10.A-V)
  20 photographs (postcards included) pertaining to Pres. and Mrs. Warren G. Harding's trip to Alaska on the U.S.S. Henderson. Mr. Jessey was a crew member on the ship.
- Job (Martha) Collection, 568 photos / 3 envelopes (Box 74056 - 10.A-V)
  - 1 photo album containing 360 photos relating to trip to China aboard Empress of Asia, including visits to Tientsin, Peking, Soochon, Mokan Shan, Shanghai, 1919 (Folder fA)
    Includes photos of Y.W.C.A activities.
  - 1 photo album containing 190 photos relating to trip to China, 1925 (Folder fB)
    Includes photos of Y.W.C.A activities in end of Sacred Island of Buddhists in Poo Too.
  - 18 photos relating to the Temple of Confucius, Temple of heaven, Lama Temple in Sianfu, Camel Back Bridge Summer Palace Peking, Nedle Pagoda in Hangchow, Altar of Heaven, The White Pagoda, Yellow Temple, National Headquarters Building Y.W.C.A of China, undated (Folder mC)